What was that?
Kawachi
Yeah... Sure...
I was just about to get up...
Oh, I see. Got it.
Don't worry about it.
We'll meet to bargain with them early next week, all right?
Talk to you later.
My grandfather died last night.
That dream I had...
Was that Grandpa...
and Mom?
Seems he'd lost touch with the family...
I come back after all this time and it's for a funeral...
I dunno about tomorrow
It's different than a sacrifice Something's off
I don't think it's like some penalty game
So, why? I don't get it at all
I'm a little bit unsatisfied, but your presence
right now is more than just important
There's no such thing in this world
as something never-ending
Crying isn't painful, it's love's sweet drops, sweet drops!
I want to keep dreaming forever, ya know?
I want to be more kind, ya know?
As long as I'm with you, I'm happy
Girls sure are strong, ya know?
But sometimes we're weak, ya know?
Our wish is to be happy, happy, happy!
And those days will be happy, too!
Just wanna make you happy!
I'm here.
Oh, Daikichi, you got here fast.
Just put your bags in Grandpa's room.
Okay.
By the way, there was a girl in the yard.
Is Haruko's girl already that old?
That wasn't Reina...
Well then whose kid is she?
Darn it! This kitchen is so inconvenient!
I don't know what to do now...
Well, he was already 79 and died peacefully, didn't he?
Apparently, that girl is Grandpa's illegitimate child...
Hah?!
Grandpa's child?!
Grandpa didn't say a thing about it...
And his lover took off, too...
His lover?! He was 79!
It's so embarrassing, not to mention shameful...
Then she's...
Like your little sister...
And my aunt...
How can you joke about this?!
You're 30 years old! You should know when it's the right time to joke around.
You died in peace, huh, Grandpa?
How much should I put in?
As much as you like. It doesn't matter.
I know, but there's a standard, isn't there?
Honestly, any amount is fine...
Although these days, it's very common for sutras to be recited
and a posthumous Buddhist name to be given...
She said 400,000 to 500,000 yen.
That's a lot  of money.
Hello. It's been a long time.
Oh, Daikichi. Long time no see.
Have you been busy?
Yeah, busy enough...
You always say you're busy! Too busy to even visit your own mother...
He didn't even come home for New Year's.
Stop running! Reina!
Stop it! Reina!
Haruko!
Oh, Dai! Long time no see!
Mama!
Reina!
Gotcha!
Now be a good girl and don't run around!
No way! I don't wanna!
What?
Nothing...
You look a lot like your grandfather when he was younger...
Daikichi, did you hear?
Yeah, from mom earlier...
I wonder if it's true.
I'm sure my elder brother was lonely living alone, but...
Apparently, there's a maternity health record book.
It says her name is Rin.
Nevertheless, we're talking about a 79-year-old man...
Well, besides  what your father would or wouldn't have done,
I still think it's pretty impressive....
Daikichi, would you bring the cushions out of the closet for me?
Sure.
What?
Hey...
Let's swap!
No!
Leave it like it is!
I did it!
Hey, look! Look!
Reina, don't run!
Oh, how clever!
Is it pretty?
It certainly is! You're very good at cat's cradle, Reina!
Next, try to make a four-square ladder!
Mmm...
Oh, my, Reina... Here, let me show you...
Uh-uh!
Poop bomb!
Stop it this instant, Reina!
Uncle, Uncle...
You can go to sleep first.
I'll take my turn watching the incense.
I-If you insist...
Hey, don't sleep in here!
Let's get some rest over there.
What about the incense?
Daikichi says he'll watch over it...
Oof...
Take care of my big brother...
You get some sleep too.
I'm fine...
Look at that mug...
All right, everyone...
Please make your final farewells.
Rest in peace.
Big brother...
Grandpa...
I'll see you soon.
Come along, Reina.
Okay!
It's time to say goodbye to Grandpa.
Okay.
A field of flowers!
Stop it!
No! I'm making a field of flowers!
I wanna make it!
You come over here and say goodbye as well.
Place these on Grandpa.
Hey!
Bellflower...
Grandpa loved that flower...
That flower makes Grandpa happiest.
He's not going to wake up again?
No. He's not going to wake up.
You really are his daughter, aren't you?
Where did this Yoshii Masako go?
I don't think any good will come from finding someone
who can abandon her child and run away.
How utterly irresponsible!
My big brother was stubborn about it...
Watch it!
That girl can't talk!
Annoying, huh?
And she still has all of her baby teeth!
She can talk!
And she's not annoying!
She can't talk!
That's why it's so boring being with her!
Here! You can have all these if you go away!
You're like a candy man!
Sorry, Dai.
The most important thing is,
who's going to take care of that child right now?
Well, I can't.
Not while I have the store to run.
Maybe if she were a little better behaved...
And she doesn't like to talk either.
Mom...
You're at home all the time. Why don't you take her in for a while?
Y-You know that's impossible!
I don't have that much free time on my hands!
Do you understand how hard it is to raise a child?!
Haven't I made enough sacrifices over the years?!
I'd feel sorry for the girl if she came over
and no one had the time to look after her.
Wasn't this meeting supposed to be about who would take in Rin?
It's not like you're going to do anything anyway, right brother?
Think about this more seriously.
I'm not even certain that she is Grandpa's child.
See? You haven't thought it through so you can't even give me a comeback.
For now, I say we try placing her in a facility as quickly as possible...
What?
Rin!
Wanna come home with me?
Hey! Daikichi!
Brother?!
Old man, I'm hungry...
O-Old man...?!
Don't call me an old man!
After all, you're my aunt!
A sunny early Sunday afternoon
Let's go somewhere today
It's the same road I'm used to traveling
But I can see it sparkling so bright
With the sun shining down its warmth
And you here by my side...
I'm already high, high, high
I feel like dashing out
Sing, la, la, la
My voice reaches forever
I'm already high, high, high
Ride the dancing wind
Sing, la, la, la
My voice springs up
Is it good?
Uh-huh.
More?
All we have left is rice.
I'll make a rice ball...
I don't have anything to put in the rice ball.
Salt!
Salt?
Hey! That's still hot!
Look!
But it'll have a tender taste.
Here, Grandpa.
I mean Daikichi!
Daikichi is strange too...
It's good.